A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Technology, 2000-2009 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Legislative files, 2006-2009., Extent: 1.8 cu. ft. (4 boxes)
  - HB 2426 (May): Government Data Collection and Dissemination Practices Act; extends implementation of prohibition, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - HB 2427 (May): Protection of Social Security Numbers Act; first five digits to be confidential from disclosure, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - HB 2444 (Sickles): Biotech, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - HB 2455 (O'Bannon): Biosciences and other technology industries; qualified equity and subordinated debt investments, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - HB 2497 (Nixon): Electronic government; Secretary of Technology to develop and implement strategies therefor, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - HB 2508 (Pollard): E-filing with state agencies, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - HB 2665 (May): Va. Broadband Infrastructure Loan Fund, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - HB 2539 (Nixon): Enterprise Applications, Division of; established within VITA, appoint Chief Applications Officer, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - HB 2539 (Nixon): Enterprise Applications, Division of; established within VITA, appoint Chief Applications Officer, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Series IV. Information Technology Investment Board, 2006-2009., Extent: 1.8 cu. ft. (4 boxes)
  Meeting material, 2006-2009, related to the Information Technology Investment Board, an independent board to which the Chief Information Officer reported until it was reorganized in 2010. The Secretary of Technology was an ex-officio member of the board and served as its vice-chair. Includes updates from the Chief Information Officer, the Virginia Enterprise Applications Program, and the Recommended Technology Investment Projects, as well as financial information and other presentations given to the Information Technology Investment Board.
  Chronological.
  - ITIB Orientation Guide, 2006 January 3. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2006 February 9. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - ITIB Commonwealth IT Solutions Committee, 2006 April 5. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2006 April 6. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - ITIB Commonwealth IT Solutions Committee, 2006 July 19. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2006 July 20. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2006 August 10. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2006 October 19. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2007 January 18. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2007 April 18. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2007 July 18-19. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Recommended Technology Investment Projects Report for the 2008-2010 Biennium, 2007. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2007 October 18. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - ITIB Executive Evaluation and Governance Committee, 2007 December 18. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2008 January 17. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2008 April 17. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2008 July 17. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2008 October 16. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2008 November 19. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2009 January 15. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2009 March 30. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - ITIB Meeting, 2009 April 16. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Recommended Technology Investment Projects Report for the 2010-2012 Biennium, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 6)